// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Who is the CEO of Oneness Labs?",
        answer: "Kathy Gong",
        options: [
            "Kathy Gong",
            "0xWest",
            "Tao",
            "Dimlak"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What is the Oneness Matrix?",
        answer: "An operating system for the gaming universe",
        options: [
            "A game developed by Oneness Labs",
            "An operating system for the gaming universe",
            "A blockchain protocol",
            "A virtual reality headset"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the primary goal of Oneness Labs?",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "To integrate traditional gaming with the blockchain ecosystem",
            "To create the world's first gaming-intent layer",
            "To facilitate widespread acceptance of Web3 gaming",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is the Oneness IPverse?",
        answer: "A transformative initiative around game intellectual properties",
        options: [
            "A blockchain protocol",
            "A transformative initiative around game intellectual properties",
            "A virtual reality headset",
            "A social media platform"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is One Spark?",
        answer: "The cornerstone NFT within the Oneness Labs ecosystem",
        options: [
            "A game developed by Oneness Labs",
            "A virtual reality headset",
            "A blockchain protocol",
            "The cornerstone NFT within the Oneness Labs ecosystem"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Where does the adventure take place in the Oneness Matrix?",
        answer: "In the enchanting city of Onar",
        options: [
            "In the dark realms of the internet",
            "In the bustling streets of New York City",
            "In the enchanted forests of Avalon",
            "In the enchanting city of Onar"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the supply of One Spark NFTs?",
        answer: "1,000",
        options: [
            "100",
            "1,000",
            "10,000",
            "100,000"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the mint date for One Spark?",
        answer: "May 2024",
        options: [
            "March 2024",
            "April 2024",
            "May 2024",
            "June 2024"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What network is used for One Spark minting?",
        answer: "BTC",
        options: [
            "ETH",
            "BTC",
            "BSC",
            "ADA"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the goal of Oneness Labs?",
        answer: "To migrate the $200 billion traditional gaming industry to Web3",
        options: [
            "To become the biggest gaming company in the world",
            "To dominate the cryptocurrency market",
            "To migrate the $200 billion traditional gaming industry to Web3",
            "To create the first fully decentralized virtual world"
        ]
    }
    // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
    // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9.....
  ];
  